New York City Office of Collective Bargaining Records 5154
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York City Office of Collective Bargaining Records
1968-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York City Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB)
5154
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Collection includes: Decisions, Releases, cases, fact-finding reports, Annual reports, impasse panel reports. Divided into 5 series: 1. Releases 2. Decisions from Board of Collective Bargaining. 3. Decisions from Board of Certification 4. Impasses Pane (or Arbitration Board) Decisions 5. Arbitration Cases
5555842
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 30, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, November 01, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5921m: New York City Office of Collective Bargaining Historical Materials
Collective bargaining -- Municipal employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- New York (State) -- New York; Collective bargaining -- New York (State) -- New York; Government employee unions -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (N.Y.) Office of Collective Bargaining
5555842
- Miscellaneous papers 1966-1980 and undated; Board of Certification, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
  - Briefs, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1966-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Statutory Changes, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reports, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports and Revised Rules of the Office of Collective Bargaining; and New York City Collective Bargaining Law, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Indexes (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Certification Decisions (Summary Digest) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Releases, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    Case Numbers 2-3
  - Releases, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Case Numbers 1-21
  - Releases, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Case Numbers 1-28
  - Releases, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Case Numbers 1 and 3
  - Releases, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Case Numbers 4-18
  - Releases, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Case Numbers 22-26
  - News, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Case Numbers A-11 - A-68
  - Board of Certification, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Case Numbers 58-80
  - Impasse, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Case Numbers I-2 - I28
  - Board of Certification, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Case Numbers 1-15
  - Board of Certification, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Case Numbers 16-40
  - Board of Certification, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Case Numbers 41-55
  - Board of Certification, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Case Numbers 56-71
  - Impasse, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Case Numbers I2-I28
  - Board of Certification, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board of Certification, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Case Numbers 16-50
  - Board of Certification, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Case Numbers 51-65
  - Board of Certification, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Case Numbers 66-80
- Board of Certification, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
  - Board of Certification, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Case Numbers 81-98
  - Impasse, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Case Numbers I-54 - I-69
  - Board of Certification, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Certification, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Case Numbers 16-25
  - Board of Certification, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Case Numbers 26-40
  - Board of Certification, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Case Numbers 41-65
  - Board of Certification, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Case Numbers 66-84
  - Impasse, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Case Number I-75
  - Board of Certification, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board of Certification, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Case Numbers 16-30
  - Board of Certification, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Case Numbers 31-45
  - Board of Certification, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Case Numbers 46-60
  - Board of Certification, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Case Numbers 61-77
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Case Numbers 1-10
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Case Numbers 11-15
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Case Numbers 26-44
- Board of Certification, 1973-1978 (Box 3)
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Case Numbers 45-50
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Case Numbers 51-60
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Case Numbers 61-70
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Case Numbers 71-85
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Case Numbers 86-100
  - Board of Certification, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Case Numbers 101-115
  - Impasse, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board of Certifications, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Case Numbers 1-20
  - Board of Certifications, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Case Numbers 21-40
  - Board of Certification, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Case Numbers 41-51
  - Board of Certification, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Case Numbers 52-61
  - Board of Certification, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Case Numbers 62-70
  - Board of Certification, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Case Numbers 71-75
  - Board of Certification, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Board of Certification, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Case Numbers 21-45
  - Board of Certification, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Case Numbers 46-63
  - Board of Certification, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Case Numbers 1-30
  - Board of Certification, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Case Numbers 30-60
  - Board of Certification, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Case Numbers 1-40
  - Board of Certification, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Board of Certification, 1978-1995; Board of Collective Bargaining 1968-1973 (Box 4)
  - Board of Certification, 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Amendments, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Case Numbers 1-3
  - Board of Certification, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Certification, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of Certification, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board of Certification, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board of Certification, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board of Certification, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board of Certification, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board of Certification, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board of Certification, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Board of Certification, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board of Certification, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board of Certification, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Board of Certification, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Case Numbers 20-40
  - Board of Certification, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Case Numbers 1-39
  - Board of Certification, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Case Number 1
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Case Numbers 10-16
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Case Numbers 1-9
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Case Numbers 1-6
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Case Numbers 7-12
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Case Numbers 14-21
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Case Numbers 10-19
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Case Numbers 20-25
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Case Numbers 1-7
- Board of Collective Bargaining, 1974-1983 (Box 5)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Case Numbers 1-22
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Case Numbers 11-20
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Case Numbers 21-30
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Case Numbers 1-31
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Board of Collective Bargaining, 1984-1989 (Box 6)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Board of Collective Bargaining, 1990-1995 (Box 7)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Board of Collective Bargaining, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)